Ayush Kumar Singh

UX Engineer

ayush.singh.xda@gmail.com • +91 7011 439 788 • Noida, India

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a self-taught UI/UX Designer and Front end developer. I bridge the gap between Designers and Developers by serving different roles on different occasions. I like to take responsibility for crafting end to end User Experience from prototyping to develop the actual product. "Jack of all trades, master of none. Often better than the master of one."

WORK EXPERIENCE



DLT UI/UX DESIGNER

DLT Labs Private Limited, Noida

December 2019 - PRESENT



UX ENGINEER

SOE Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Noida

July 2019 - November 2019



I UX ENGINEER

Software Incubator, AKGEC

September 2016 - May 2019

SKILLS

- Javascript
- Angular
- HTML/CSS
- Git
- SVG Animation
- User Interface Design
- UX Design
- Responsive Web Design

TOOLS

- Figma, Sketch, Invision
- Adobe Creative Cloud

EDUCATION



AJAY KUMAR GARG ENGINEERING COLLEGE, (AKTU)

2015-2019

Elementary Education

DMA, Meerut (CBSE)

2004-2014

ACHIEVEMENTS

- HTML / CSS Mentor at Workshop, SDC-SI, AKGEC, 2018
- 1st position at Web Design hackathon, IMSUC, 2017
- SVG Mentor at Workshop, SDC-SI, AKGEC, 2017
- 1st position in Web and Graphic Design hackathon, ABES ACM 2017
- 1st position at Web Design hackathon, IMSUC, 2016
- Lead Designer at AKGEC College Fest, 2016
- Recognized Themer at xda-developers.com, 2014

EXTRAS

Competitive Powerlifting

- 1st position, AKGEC, 2018
- 2nd position, AKGEC 2017
- 2nd position, COT GBPU, 2017
- 2nd position, AKGEC 2016